(Leonard:)Yeah, time's gonna fly by.
(Penny:)I haven't been on a job
interview in years.
(Penny:)I'm really nervous.
(Bernadette:)Don't be.
(Bernadette:)You are built for
pharmaceutical sales.
(Bernadette:)You're cute,
you're flirty and...
(Bernadette:)Started that like there
were gonna be three things.
(Sheldon:)I don't have
any experience in sales.
(Penny:)Unless you count the bikini
car wash I did in high school.
(Penny:)But you already made me
take that off my résumé.
(Bernadette:)This job is a lot
like being a waitress,
(Bernadette:)except instead of
pushing the fish tacos
(Bernadette:)'cause they're
about to go bad,
(Bernadette:)you're just pushing
our antidepressants
(Bernadette:)before the FDA finds out they
may cause rectal bleeding.
(Penny:)They do?
(Sheldon:)Maybe.
(Bernadette:)But like our lawyers say,
the world is full of things
(Bernadette:)that can cause a
rectum to bleed.
(Bernadette:)Anyway, I talked
you up to Dan.
(Bernadette:)He's the guy who'll
be interviewing you.
(Penny:)Oh, I really appreciate this.
(Penny:)I just hope I'm not
in over my head.
(Bernadette:)You'll be fine.
Just be yourself.